Crusade for Opportunity Records
Crusade for Opportunity Records
- Education Division
  - Library
    - Boston, Action for Boston Community Development
      - Negotiations and Commitments on other Sources of Financial Support, 1964 (Box 215)
      - Personnel Policies manual, 1965 (Box 215)
      - Research Guidelines for the Boston Youth Opportunities Project, 1962 (Box 215)
      - Sources of Financial Support for Boston Youth Opportunites Project, 1966 (Box 215)
      - Youth Training and Employment Program, Progress Report, 1964-1965; 3 folders (Box 215)
    - Boston Juvenile Court, Citizenship Training Group, Inc., Biennial Report, 1962-1963 (Box 215)
    - Bosworth, Claud A, Summary to Steps Taken by Northern Michigan University to Initiate, Secure Approval and Implement Project MDS41-64 with the Office of Manpower, Automation, and Training, 1964 (Box 215)
    - Bottrell, Harold R, Using Community Resources Within the Curriculum, 1960 (Box 215)
    - Brainin, Jema, Mobilization for Youth, Language Skills, Formal Education and the Lower Class Child, 1964 (Box 215)
    - Campbell and Hall, Inc., 1966 (Box 215)
    - Carmen Educational Associates Limitied, 1964 (Box 215)
    - Catholic Charities, 1966 (Box 215)
    - Center for the Study of Unemployed Youth, Educational Deficiencies of Disadvantaged Youth, 1965 (Box 215)
    - Charles Burke, undated (Box 215)
    - Cloward, Richard A, James A Jones, New York School of Social Work, Columbia University, Social Class: Educational Attitudes and Participation, Jul 1962 (Box 215)
    - Colonial Films, Incorporated, 1965 (Box 215)
    - Communities in Action, Bookbinders Statement, 1966 (Box 215)
    - Community Chest and Council, Library Classification, 1964 (Box 215)
    - Congressional acts, 1961-1966 (Box 215)
    - Croft Educational Services, 1966 (Box 216)
    - Curriculum Materials Corporation, undated (Box 216)
    - Curtis Circulation Company, 1966 (Box 216)
    - Dancis, Joseph, Your Premature Baby, 1966 (Box 216)
    - Davis, William G, Lunchen Address, Canadian National Exhibition, Young Canada's Day, Toronto, August 19, 1963 (Box 216)
    - Day Care for your Child in a Family Home, 1964 (Box 216)
    - Delorme, Jean, Specialized Education in the Province of Quebec, 1963 (Box 216)
    - Deitrick, Sarah S (with Dorothy E. Bradbury), The International Activities of the Children's Bureau, 1961 (Box 216)
    - Des Moines, Iowa, Council of Social Agencies, OMAT Project, Final Report, Jun-Jul 1965 (Box 216)
    - Des Moines, Iowa, Iowa State Manpower Development Council, Sixth Progress Report, 1966 (Box 216)
    - Deutscher, Irwin
      - Continuity in Sociological Theory, 1963 (Box 216)
      - Low Income Housing in Syracuse, New York, Needs and Recommendations, 1963 (Box 216)
      - Pressure from Outside: A Perspective for the Mayor's Commission for Youth, 1963 (Box 216)
      - Some Relevant Directions for Research in Juvenile Delinquency, 1963 (Box 216)
      - Then and Now: Regionalism in American Sociology, 1937-1962, 1963 (Box 216)
      - Youth Development Center, circa 1963 (Box 216)
    - Detroit Commission on Children and Youth, Annual Report, 1961 (Box 216)
    - Detroit, Eastern Community Action Center, Information and Education, 1965 (Box 216)
    - Detroit Great Cities Project, Working Toward More Effective Education, A Report on the Detroit Great Cities Project After One Year, 1961 (Box 216)
    - Detroit Mayor's Commission, On the Spot, 1964 (Box 216)
    - Detroit Mayor's Committee for Community Action for Detroit Youth, A Challenge to Qualified Research…, circa 1963 (Box 216)
    - DeWees, Dan and Robert Schrank, The Recruitment and Training of Crew Chiefs in the Urban Youth Work Corps, Mobilization for Youth, 1966 (Box 216)
    - Dince, Paul R., MD, Some Causative Factors in the Development of Antisocial Behavior, 1966 (Box 216)
    - Directions and info, 1965 (Box 216)
    - Dodson, Dan W., Education and the Powerless, 1964 (Box 216)
    - Donohue, George, American Workers on the Move, 1962 (Box 216)
    - Donahue, Maurice F.X., On Group Work: An Untrained Sub-professional Speaks His Mind, 1964 (Box 216)
    - Dover Publications, Inc., 1965 (Box 216)
    - Draper Correctional Center, Elmora Alabama, Experimental and Demonstration Project, Fifth Progress Report, May-Jun 1965 (Box 216)
    - Draper Correctional Center, Elmora Alabama, Experimental and Demonstration Manpower Project, Sixth Progress Report, 1965 (Box 216)
    - Dunham, Arthur, Principles of Community Development, 1966 (Box 216)
    - DuPont, 1965 (Box 216)
    - Durham, North Carolina, Operation Breakthrough, Personnel Status Report, 1966 (Box 216)
    - Educational Audio Visual, Inc., 1965 (Box 217)
    - Educational Opportunities Project, 1966 (Box 217)
    - Educational Reading Service, Inc, undated (Box 217)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica Filmstrips, undated (Box 217)
    - Eye Gate House, Inc., 1966 (Box 217)
    - Fall and spring program plans, 1965 (Box 217)
    - Films Incorporated, 1967 (Box 217)
    - Flint Schools' Experimental Program for the Emotionally Handicapped, The Classroom Human Relations Program, 1964 (Box 217)
    - Flint Schools' Experimental Program for the Emotionally Handicapped, The Social Adjustment Room Program, 1964 (Box 217)
    - Folkways Records, 1966 (Box 217)
    - Goldman, Nathan, The Disposition of Juvenile Arrests by Urban Police, 1964 (Box 217)
    - Goldman, Nathan, Proposed In-service Training for 1965 (Box 217)
    - Golden Press, Inc., undated (Box 217)
    - Gordon, Edmond W, Counseling Youth Who Are Handicapped by Social Status Differences, 1963 (Box 217)
    - Grand Rapids, United Community Service, Big Brother Application and copy of initial planning division report, 1965 (Box 217)
    - Grier, Eunice (with George Grier), Equality and Beyond: Housing Segregation in the Great Society, 1966 (Box 217)
    - Grimes, John A, Teenage Job Woes, Youth Unemployment Soars as Demand for Unskilled Labor, 1963 (Box 217)
    - Grosser, Charles F, Community Development Programs Serving the Urban Poor, undated (Box 217)
    - Grosser, Charles F, The Program of Mobilization for Youth, 1964 (Box 217)
    - Guidance Associates, undated (Box 217)
    - Harvey House, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 217)
    - Head Start, pamphlets, 1966 (Box 217)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1966 (Box 217)
    - Imperial Film Company, Inc., undated (Box 217)
    - Imperial Productions, Inc., 1966 (Box 217)
    - Institute for Teachers of Indian Children, Training Center for Delinquency Prevention and Control, 1965 (Box 217)
    - The Institute of Educational Research, Inc., Evaluated of the Progressive Choice Reading Method, undated (Box 217)
    - Jam Handy Organization, 1967 (Box 217)
    - Job Corps, Admissions Manual, 1966 (Box 218)
    - Job Corps, Sargent Shriver, 1965-1966 (Box 218)
    - Job Upgrading Project, Neighborhood House, monthly report, 1966 (Box 218)
    - Jones, James A, The American Negro and the Current Scene, 1964 (Box 218)
    - Jones, Wyatt and Robert Ontell, Discontinuities in the Social Treatment of Juvenile Offenders, 1963 (Box 218)
    - Keller, Suzanne, The Social World of the Urban Slum Child Some Early Findings, 1963 (Box 218)
    - Lane County Youth Project, First Year Demonstration Programs, 1964 (Box 218)
    - Lane County Youth Project, Those Who Fail, 1965 (Box 218)
    - La Vietes, Ruth L, School and Community Course, Motivation and Behavior Control, 1963 (Box 218)
    - Legislative Notes, 88th Congress, Office of Education, progress reports, 1963-1964 (Box 218)
    - Legislative Notes, 89th Congress, 1st session, Office of Education, progress reports, 1965; 2 folders (Box 218)
    - Legislative Notes, 89th Congress, 2nd session, Office of Education, progress reports, 1966 (Box 218)
    - Library acquisitions, 1965 (Box 218)
    - Library filmstrip center, undated (Box 218)
    - Library lists, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 218)
    - Listening Library, Inc., 1966 (Box 218)
    - Maps: County by Census Tracts, 1960 (Box 218)
    - Map: Percentage of families with annual income less than $3000 a year, 1960 (Box 218)
    - Map: Percentage of housing units substandard in the county, 1960 (Box 218)
    - Map: School districts in Onondaga County, undated (Box 219)
    - Mead, Margaret, The Changing Cultural Patterns of Work and Leisure, US Dept of Labor, 1966 (Box 219)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 219)
    - Mobilization for Youth
      - A Handbook for Parents, Jun 1964 (Box 219)
      - New Developments in the Puerto Rican Community of NYC, 1964 (Box 219)
      - Perspective on the Reading Controversy: Phonics Versus Whole-World, 1964 (Box 219)
      - Project of the Center for Programmed Instruction, Progress Report #1, 1963 (Box 219)
      - The World of Education, 1962 (Box 219)
    - Mountain Plains Film Library Association, 1965-1966 (Box 219)
    - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, Trends in Housing, 1966 (Box 219)
    - National Committee for Children and Youth, project report, "A Program of Multioccupational Training, Counseling, Employment, Followup and Community Support for Youthful Offenders", 1966 (Box 219)
    - New acquisitions, 1966 (Box 219)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1966 (Box 219)
    - NYS Department of Labor, Industrial Bulletin, 1966 (Box 219)
    - Oakland City College, an excerpt of Workshop on Cultural Diversity, written under the direction of Joseph D. Lohman, 1964 (Box 219)
    - Observations, employment 1963, Dr. Julius Cohen (Box 219)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, CAP Memos, 1966 (Box 219)
    - Pamphlets for Curriculum Central Technical High School, undated (Box 219)
    - Poverty and Human Resources Abstracts, 1966 (Box 219)
    - Printed laws, 1958-1962 (Box 219)
    - Printed laws, 1963-1966; 7 folders (Box 220)
    - Quebec Dept. of Public Instruction, Orienation for Girls and Boys, Who Finish Elementary and Secondary School, 1962 (Box 220)
    - Quebec Ministry of Youth, correspondence courses prospectus, 1963 (Box 220)
    - Quincy, Illnois Youth Development Project, Excerpts from Reseach Interviews with Students who have Dropped out of High School, 1959 (Box 220)
    - Rabb, Herbert, A View of Reading in Relation to the Total Curriculum, undated (Box 220)
    - Randolph, Appalachian regional development program carries into constructive…, 1966 (Box 220)
    - RCA Victor, 1966 (Box 220)
    - Reissman, Frank
      - New Approaches to Mental Health Treatment for Labor and Low Income Groups, 1964 (Box 220)
      - New Models for Treatment Approach to Low-Income Clients, 1963 (Box 221)
      - The Non-deferred Gratification Pattern: A Critique, 1958 (Box 221)
      - The Revolution in Social Work: The New Nonprofessional, 1963 (Box 221)
      - School Culture, Learning Culture, and the Cognitive Style of the Disadvantaged, 1962 (Box 221)
      - The Third Force: An Anti-Poverty Ideology, undated (Box 221)
      - Training the Non-Professional, 1967 (Box 221)
    - Report on the Vocational Advisory Service Youth and Work program, 1962-1965 (Box 221)
    - Rural opportunities, 1966 (Box 221)
    - Saleem, Betty L, The Neglected Dropout: The Returnee, 1963 (Box 221)
    - Samuels, Gertrude, Even More Crucial Than In the South, 1963 (Box 221)
    - Sandak, Inc., undated (Box 221)
    - Sarnoff, Robert W, Address at the Bethany College Commencement, Bethany West Virginia, June 6, 1965 (Box 221)
    - Saunders, Lyle, Family-planning Research and Evaluation Needs for the Future, 1966 (Box 221)
    - Sawyer, Michael D, Factors determining residential distribution of the non-white population (Box 221)
    - Scheuer, James H, Scheuer Amendment to the Economic Opportunity Act, Community Action, Adult Work Training and Employment Programs, 1966 (Box 221)
    - Schiffman, Jacob
      - Employment of High School Graduates and Dropouts in 1961, 1962 (Box 221)
      - Employment of High School Graduates and Dropouts in 1962 (Box 221)
      - Marital and Family Characteristics of Workers, March 1960, 1961 (Box 221)
      - Marital Status of Workers, 1959, 1960 (Box 221)
      - Multiple Jobholders in May 1962, 1963 (Box 221)
    - Scholz, Bernard W, Medicine in the Slums, 1963 (Box 221)
    - School of Education Reading Center and University College, Adult Education Division, SU, Reading Camps in the Adirondacks, 1963 (Box 221)
    - Schools Program Community Action for Youth, An Interium Evaluation (Box 221)
    - Schreiber, Daniel
      - The Dropout and the Delinquent: Promising Practices Gleaned from a Year of Study, 1963 (Box 221)
      - Dropouts and Incompetence, undated (Box 221)
      - Juvenile Delinquency and the School Dropout Problem, 1963 (Box 221)
      - The School Dropout, Fugitive from Failure, 1962 (Box 221)
      - A School's Work with Urban Disadvantaged Pupils, 1962 (Box 221)
    - Selective Service: One-Third of a Nation, Report on Men Found Unqualified for Military Service, 1964 (Box 222)
    - Sellard, Dan, Smile - You're on Candid Classroom, 1966 (Box 222)
    - "Settlement House and the Attack on Urban Poverty," Herbert Gans, 1963 (Box 222)
    - The Spoken Word, Inc., undated (Box 222)
    - Stanley Bowmar Co., Inc., undated; 2 folders (Box 222)
    - Survey of Police Arrests and Dispositions; An Analysis of Recidivision Involving Juvenile, Youthful, and Adult Offenders, 1963 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Action for Youth: Proposal Summary, 1964 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Board of Education, Central Technical High School, 1963 (Box 222)
    - Syracyuse Board of Education, Special Programs, 1962 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Book Center, Preview of Report from a Chinese Village," by Aldius Huxley, 1965 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Business and Professional Women's Club, Outline of Local Government, 1964 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Central Technical High School, Followship Study on Central High Graduates 1949-1962 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse, City School District, Madison Area Project: Vocational Orientation Weekend, 1963 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse, City of, Supplement to the Charter of the City of Syracuse, 1964 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Conference on Human Rights and Housing Report, The Next Steps Toward Equality of Opportunity in the Syracuse Metro Area, Jul 1962 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse CORE, Project 101: Toward Social Justice, 1964; 2 folders (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Health Department, Bureau of Nursing, Annual Report 1962 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Health Department, Syracuse Health Headlines, 1965 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse map, 1961 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Mayor's Commission for Youth, 1960 Census Data (Box 222)
    - Syracuse paper clippings, 1964-1967 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Public Library, Annual Report of the Director, 1964 (Box 222)
    - Syracuse Public School District, Tentative Industrial Arts Curriculum, Jr. High, 1963 (Box 223)
    - Syracuse Public School System, Central Technical High School Curriculums, 1963 (Box 223)
    - Syracuse Schools and populations, undated (Box 223)
    - Syracuse School District, Madison Area Project, World of Work Training Program, 1963 (Box 223)
    - Syracuse University, Proposal for a Community Development, Demonstration Training and Research Project, Dec 1964 (Box 223)
    - Syracuse University Alumni News, Youth Development Center Reports, 1961 (Box 223)
    - Syracuse University, Youth Development Center
      - Higher Horizons, 1961 (Box 223)
      - Information Bulletin, 1960 (Box 223)
      - Reports, Growing Up in the City, 1961 (Box 223)
      - A summary of a little score project for the Syracuse Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1963 (Box 223)
      - Youth and Work Evaluation Project, Dropouts Tell Their Story, undated (Box 223)
    - Syracuse YMCA, Annual report of the YMCA, 1964 (Box 223)
    - Tannenbaum, Abraham, Curriculum Perspective for Slum Schools, undated (Box 223)
    - Tauber, Karl E, Residential Segragation, 1965 (Box 223)
    - Taylor, Harold C, What the Individual Firm Can Do to Contribute to Business Stabilization, 1962 (Box 223)
    - Teffertelle, Ruth S, Delinquency Prevention Through Revitalizing Parent-Child Relations, 1960 (Box 223)
    - Temple University Center for Community Studies, Dialect Remediation Project, Bi-Monthly Report, Sep-Oct 1965 (Box 223)
    - Temple University Center for Community Studies, Dialect Remdial Program, Final Report, 1964-1965 (Box 223)
    - Thomas, Harry Harvey (Mrs.), Simplified Parliamentary Procedure, Based on Robert's Rules of Order, 1965 (Box 223)
    - Thomas, Margaret W., A Study of Specialized Nursing Positions and Personnel in Official State and Local Maternal and Crippled Children's Programs, 1962 (Box 223)
    - Thornton, Charles B, Remarks at Job Corps Anniversary, Mar 1966 (Box 223)
    - Tibbitts, Clark, Employment of the Older Work: Two Papers and a Bibliography, 1959 (Box 223)
    - Til, William Van, Prejudiced, How Do People Get That Way?, undated (Box 223)
    - Tillman, James A, Study Paper for Program Development and Funding, 1966 (Box 223)
    - A Training Institute for Differentiation and Remediation of the Learning Problems of Culturally Impoverished Children, 1965 (Box 223)
    - Training Series for Social Agencies: Bibliography on Education, Drop-outs, and Youth Employment, 1965 (Box 223)
    - Transaction Social Science and Modern Society: Social Action on the Installment Plan, 1966 (Box 223)
    - Turner, John B, The Continuing Debate: Community Organization or Community Planning?, 1963 (Box 223)
    - Tyson, Cyril, Integrated Educational Experiences, 1964 (Box 223)
    - United Arab Republic, Information Department, The New Port Said in 1963 (Box 223)
    - United Community Chest and Council of Onondaga County, Inc.
      - Camp Directory, 1966 (Box 223)
      - Nursery Schools, 1966 (Box 223)
      - Nursery Schools Directory, 1964-1965 (Box 223)
      - Nursery Schools and Child Care Services, 1965 (Box 224)
      - Special Report on Resident Summer Camp, 1962 (Box 224)
      - Summary of a Proposal to Continue the Action Area Planning Service, 1965 (Box 224)
    - United Community Funds and Council of America, Inc., Local Developments in the War Against Poverty, 1964 (Box 224)
    - University College, Syracuse University, Community Action Training Center, 1965 (Box 224)
    - U.S. Censuses of Population and Housing: 1960 Census Tracts, Syracuse, NY, 1961 (Box 224)
    - US Chamber of Commerce, Businessmen Urge You to Stay in School, 1964 (Box 224)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture
      - Agricultural Marketing Service, Direct Food Distribution Program, 1963 (Box 224)
      - Agricultural Marketing Service, Food Stamp Program: A Method for Sharing our Agricultural Abundance, 1964 (Box 224)
      - Consumer and Marketing Service, The US Department of Agriculture's Food Donation Programs, 1965 (Box 224)
      - Economic Research Service, Urban and Rural Levels of Living, 1960 (Box 224)
      - Et al, Federal assisistance for water and sewer systems and sewage treatment works, 1965 (Box 224)
      - FCS, Co-ops have a place in rural community progress, 1961 (Box 224)
      - FCS, How farmer cooperative services works, 1962 (Box 224)
      - FCS, Rural credit unions of the US, 1966 (Box 224)
      - FCS, Using Your Rural Credit Union, 1966 (Box 224)
      - Farmer's Home Association
        - Emergency Loans, 1966 (Box 224)
        - Farmers home administration insured loans: information for lenders, 1965 (Box 224)
        - Farm labor housing loans and grants, 1966 (Box 224)
        - Financial assistance to small towns and rural groups: water systems and waste disposal systems, 1966 (Box 224)
        - Housing for senior citizens, 1964-1965; 2 folders (Box 224)
        - Loans for forestry purposes, 1964 (Box 224)
        - Loans for water development and soil conservation, 1965 (Box 224)
        - Loans to cooperatives serving rural families with low income, 1965 (Box 224)
        - Need a little help? Want to make more money farming? Or start a little business? Or do a better job with the one you have? (Box 224)
        - Operating loans for better living, better farming, 1965 (Box 224)
        - Opportunity loans, loans to rural families with small incomes, 1965 (Box 224)
        - Opportunity loans for rural families with small incomes, 1965 (Box 224)
        - Rural housing loans, 1966 (Box 224)
        - Watershed loans, 1965 (Box 224)
      - Regional offices, undated (Box 224)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce
      - Bureau of Census, Characteristics of the Population, New York State, 1956-1957 (Box 224)
      - Bureau of Census, Senior Citizens, 18 Million: Numbers marital status living arrangements housing employment income assests states, 1964 (Box 224)
      - Bureau of the Census, Our Growing Population, 1960 (Box 224)
      - Bureau of the Census, Size of Family Income, By Family Characteristics, 1960 (Box 224)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
      - Administration on Aging, Background and provisions, the older americans act, 1966 (Box 224)
      - Administration on Aging, A New Day for the Older American Senior Citizens Month, May 1966, A Guide to Community Action (Box 224)
      - Administration on Aging, The New ADA: Administration on Aging, 1965 (Box 224)
      - Aging, 1965 (Box 225)
      - Bureau of Family Services
        - Community Planning in the Public Assistance Programs, 1965 (Box 225)
        - Medical Aid for Older Persons, 1963 (Box 225)
        - Public assistance to help needy people, 1966 (Box 225)
        - Public assistance under the Social Security Act, 1966 (Box 225)
        - Quality control in public assistance, 1965 (Box 225)
        - The role of public welfare in family planning, 1964 (Box 225)
      - Bureau of Federal Credit Unions
        - The Federal Credit Union Act, as amended, Jul 1964 (Box 225)
        - Federal credit union system, economic self-help, 1964 (Box 225)
        - Suggestions for completing organization and conducting first board of directors' meeting of a Federal Credit Union, 1965 (Box 225)
      - Children's Bureau
        - The Abused Child: Principles and Language for Legislation on Reporting of the Physically Abused Child, 1964 (Box 225)
        - Accidents and Children, 1963 (Box 225)
        - Attorney's part in adoption, 1964 (Box 225)
        - The care of your children's teeth, 1964 (Box 225)
        - Childcare arrangement of the nation's working mothers: A preliminary report, 1965 (Box 225)
        - Children's Bureau activities in mental retardation, 1966 (Box 225)
        - Child Welfare Services, 1966 (Box 225)
        - The Child with Cerebral Palsy, 1965 (Box 225)
        - The Child with a Cleft Palate, 1965 (Box 225)
        - The Child with Epilepsy, 1965 (Box 225)
        - The Child who is Hard of Hearing, 1966 (Box 225)
        - The Child with a Missing Arm or Leg, 1965 (Box 225)
        - The Child with Rheumatic Fever, 1965 (Box 225)
        - Children in Day Care with Focus on Health, 1967 (Box 225)
        - The Clinical Team Looks at Phenylketonuria, 1965 (Box 225)
        - Crippled Children's Program Statistics, 1963 (Box 225)
        - Criteria for assesing feasibility of mother's employment and adequacy of child-care plans, 1966; 2 folders (Box 225)
        - Daycare for other people's children in your home, 1964 (Box 225)
        - Daycare for your child in a family home, 1965 (Box 225)
        - Determining Fees for Daycare Services, 1964 (Box 225)
        - Emphasize Youth Potential: A Guideline to Coordinated Youth Action, 1965 (Box 225)
        - Facts About Children Adoptions: Adoptions in the United States, 1963 (Box 226)
        - Facts About Children's Bureau Programs, 1965 (Box 226)
        - Facts for Teenagers: Smoking, Health, and You, 1964 (Box 226)
        - Feeding Mentally Retarded Children: A Guide for Nurses Working with Families Who Have Mentally Retarded Children, 1964 (Box 226)
        - Foods Your Children Need, 1964 (Box 226)